<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SPC App</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">San Pablo City Application</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>

    <string name="action_bpo">BPLO Fill Up</string>
    <string name="home">\t \t San Pablo, officially the City of San Pablo, (Tagalog: Lungsod ng San Pablo), or simply
        known as
        San Pablo City, is a 1st class city in the province of Laguna, Philippines. According to the 2015 census, it has
        a population of 266,068 people. Located in the southern portion of Laguna province, it is one of the oldest
        cities in the Philippines. By land area, it is the largest in the province of Laguna. Its population ranks sixth
        within the province after the cities of Calamba, Santa Rosa, Biñan, San Pedro, and Cabuyao. The city is more
        popularly known as the "City of Seven Lakes" (Tagalog: Lungsod ng Pitong Lawa), referring to the Seven Lakes of
        San Pablo: Lake Sampaloc (or Sampalok), Lake Palakpakin, Lake Bunot, Lakes Pandin and Yambo, Lake Muhikap, and
        Lake Calibato. San Pablo was part of the Roman Catholic Archdiocese of Lipa since 1910. On November 28, 1967,
        it became an independent diocese and became the Roman Catholic Diocese of San Pablo.
    </string>

    <string name="home2">
        1910. On November 28, 1967, it became an independent diocese and became the Roman Catholic Diocese of San Pablo.
    </string>
    <string name="tab_govphil">The Integrated Government Philippines (iGovPhil) is a joint program of the
        Department of Information and Communications Technology (DICT) and the
        Advanced Science and Technology Institute of the Department of Science and Technology (DOST-ASTI)
    </string>
    <string name="form">I DECLARE UNDER PENALTY OF PERJURY that the
        forgoing information are true based on my personal knowledge and authentic records.
        Further, I agree to comply with the regulatory requirements and other deficiencies within thirty
        (30) days from release of the business permit.
    </string>
    <string name="gallery_">San Pablo, officially the City of San Pablo, (Tagalog: Lungsod ng San Pablo), or simply
        known as San Pablo City, is a 1st class city in the province of Laguna, Philippines. According to the 2015
        census, it has a population of 266,068 peopl
    </string>
    <string name="back"><![CDATA[<]]></string>
    <string name="forward"><![CDATA[>]]></string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
